德米纳尔 2-6 7-6⁵ 11-9 兹维列夫 · 赛后场上采访
I can't believe it.
真不敢相信
I mean, I've been coming here to the O2
我是说 我一直来O2看球
since 2009 when the Tour Finals came here.
从2009年总决赛来这里开始
I don't think I have seen a better match
我觉得我从没见过
than that.
比这更精彩的比赛
It was all on the line, Alex.
一切都押上了 亚历克斯
Or should I call you Houdini?
还是该叫你逃脱大师胡迪尼？
How have you won that?
这场你是怎么赢下来的？
Wow. What a day, huh?
哇 真是不得了的一天
And we're only halfway through it.
而且今天才过了一半
Only halfway through it.
才过了一半
Pretty good start for Team World,
世界队开局不错
but what a place to play some tennis.
不过在这里打球真是太棒了
This is special.
这很特别
Thank you guys.
谢谢大家
And yeah,
嗯
let's just have ourselves a little day, huh?
今天就好好享受一下吧
Alex,
亚历克斯
I want to say you literally left it all out there.
我想说你真的是拼尽了一切
Half of your leg is out there.
半条腿都留在场上了
Yeah. If you can notice my blood is red
是啊 你们注意到的话
as well.
我流的血也是红的
So what can I say?
我还能说什么呢？
It was a, you know, a very tough match,
这是一场非常艰难的比赛
a tough battle.
一场硬仗
I left it all out there and got fortunate
我拼尽了全力 也有点运气
in the end to get the job done and happy
最后把比赛拿下 很开心
to give some points for Team World.
能给世界队拿到分
I'm going to have to disagree with you.
这点我可不同意
You didn't get lucky.
你不是靠运气
You got tough as nails out there.
你在场上硬得像钉子
You're 6-2 down to the US Open
第一盘2比6输给
and the Roland Garros champion.
美网和法网冠军
You're a break down.
第二盘又被破发
He's serving for the match.
他都发球胜赛了
How have you turned that around?
你是怎么翻过来的？
Just stay in there, right?
就是一直顶住 对吧
Keep asking questions.
不停给他出难题
Give yourself a chance
给自己留机会
and you never know if you put the ball
谁知道呢 只要把球打进场
in the court, you might get lucky.
说不定就走运了
So that's what I did today.
我今天就是这么做的
You were the first team last year to come
去年你们成了第一支
from a deficit on the opening day
首日落后
of the Laver Cup.
还能在拉沃尔杯翻盘的队伍
You found yourself down 3-1
这次你们首日打完
after the opening day.
又是1比3落后
What was the mood in the locker room
昨晚回到更衣室
when you went back last night?
大家是什么心情？
Yeah, look,
嗯 你看
we were in the same position last year,
我们去年也是同样的处境
right?
对吧
And it worked out pretty well for us.
结果挺不错的
So, we know we can do some damage.
所以我们知道能搞出动静
We know we're the underdogs,
我们知道自己不被看好
but we also know that we can step out
但我们也知道 只要走上
on this court and light it up.
这片场地就能把它点燃
So, happy days.
所以 开心
On to the next one and let's see
接着打下一场 看看
if we can keep it going.
能不能一直赢下去